[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "MD", "VB", ":"], "qSentId": 50, "question": "But you actually expected Zimmerman to learn something from this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 51, "answer": "One could pray ...", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 59, "question": "... can you construct for me any form of rational defense for the way Zimmerman is currently behaving?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 60, "answer": "Well, I do think he's a victim of his own stupidity at this point.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}, "docId": "140217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 84, "question": "What did you make of that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 85, "answer": "Well, I really don't think God and Jesus really want to be dragged into George Zimmerman's tweeting with you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Trayvon Martin"]}, "docId": "140217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBD", "DT", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 120, "question": "Yeah, Nancy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 121, "answer": "Then told this is about God, did he find God after he shot Trayvon Martin and before he pulled the shotgun on his girlfriend or had a fight with his wife.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Nancy"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 130, "question": "But he's still a killer isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 131, "answer": "Let me finish.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "RP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "WP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "DT", ":"], "qSentId": 164, "question": "What?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 165, "answer": "Nancy, you're not -- you're totally leaving out the core part of what the jury and thank goodness you weren't on that jury because they looked at the facts and you don't want to deal with the fact that there was a ...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Florida"]}, "docId": "140217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 228, "question": "Is it an American societal or cultural issue, what is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 229, "answer": "Well, a lot of people suggest that it's a Florida issue.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 284, "question": "... that woman and they'll be dirty on the ground?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 285, "answer": "... I wouldn't if she -- I'm unarmed person and I would've be out at that time of night trying to find another black youth to get arrested, you know, he knew he wasn't supposed to be out with a gun, that was a rule of neighborhood watch.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Van Jones"]}, "docId": "140217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 287, "question": "What a surprise?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 288, "answer": "OK, Van Jones, Van Jones.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "EX", ":", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 292, "question": "Is there though a racial element to these two stories which links them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "WDT", "NNS", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 293, "answer": "I think that there -- there's a couple of things here.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 340, "question": "... all right?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 341, "answer": "I do believe...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 382, "question": "Let's get your reaction as you were talking in the break there about this Michael Dunn case?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 383, "answer": "Right.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael Dunn"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dunn"]}, "docId": "140217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 385, "question": "And we've got these two cases not dissimilar where people have (inaudible) and the option of it is two 17-year old kids have been shot dead?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "JJ", "WRB", "NNS", "VBP", ":", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 386, "answer": "I find Dunn's account to be incredible.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Nancy Grace"]}, "docId": "140217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 392, "question": "So, it makes me wonder, did the prosecution overcharge should this have been a man slaughter case?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJR", ",", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "MD", "DT", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 393, "answer": "Nancy Grace, can we, you know, she drives about gun control then.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NRA"]}, "docId": "140217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 400, "question": "How do you change that impulsive thing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 401, "answer": "Well, I think the NRA has been too successful.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 419, "question": "Does it really have any impact on them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 420, "answer": "MERCONISH: Well, it has an impact for us.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "WDT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 435, "question": "What would constitute a great legacy outside of ObamaCare for Obama?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 436, "answer": "Well, I don't know that he's going to get credit for the legacy from half of the electorate because half of the electorate as you well know has drawn a line in the sand and regardless of which way this thing goes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "NN", ",", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "CD", "VBN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "CD", "NN", ",", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "CD", "JJ", "IN", "RB", "WDT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 463, "question": "Do you think he can come through with all this stuff (ph)?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", ":", "NN", ":", "."], "aSentId": 464, "answer": "You know, it depends, if there's anything, if there's one shred of evidence, if there's one witness, if there's one e-mail out there that contradicts what he said at that marathon press conference then he's finished.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rand Paul"]}, "docId": "140217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 467, "question": "What about Rand Paul that we mentioned earlier?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RBR", "."], "aSentId": 468, "answer": "You know, I don't think that Rand Paul can lay claim to the Christie constituency.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Rand Paul"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 471, "question": "But could Rand Paul rally the core base of the party perhaps better than Chris Christie?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RBR", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 472, "answer": "I don't -- Piers, I don't think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rand Paul", "Chris Christie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Abigail Adams"]}, "docId": "140217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 482, "question": "What do we think of Michelle Obama?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 483, "answer": "Well, thank God you're not asking me about Abigail Adams.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michelle Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "140217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 524, "question": "Am I wrong to do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 525, "answer": "No, you're not wrong whatsoever, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "140217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 534, "question": "Is he horrified about the content, what do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 535, "answer": "Obviously, not at all please, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "IN", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 555, "question": "Do you think that this may draw a better line in the sand about where bonds (ph) begins and ends and genuine harassment and abused and bullying stops?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "NNS", "VBP", "NN", ":", "VBZ", "CC", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "CC", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 556, "answer": "I absolutely do, Piers and so if anything good has going to come from this, it's going to be that usually for any kind of major change to come.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 578, "question": "So, do you think it will have a big effect on people and how they're looking at this case now when they actually see this report as this come out?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 579, "answer": "Well, definitely and I think its going to be a really positive situation moving forward.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 584, "question": "Does he blame himself at all for, perhaps, encouraging the bond to a certain point?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "IN", ",", "RB", ",", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 585, "answer": "Well, Piers I'm not going to get into that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 592, "question": "I'm sure everyone is having this debate in the NFL now about how you try and take these guys you on the pitch, you want to be after murderous barbarians and metaphorically speaking and then away from the pitch to be polite, gentle people?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "RB", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "VBG", "CC", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 593, "answer": "Well, I mean that's a great question.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NFL"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Miami Dolphins"]}, "docId": "140217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 599, "question": "Have you had offers some other teams?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 600, "answer": "Well, right now the Miami Dolphins have its rights.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "POS", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 607, "question": "Should Richie Incognito be given another chance?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "VB", "NNP", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 608, "answer": "You know, that's not for me to say.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Richie Incognito"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 622, "question": "Do you think it wouldn't take a bit more time?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RBR", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 623, "answer": "UCKERMAN: Well, Piers as you know, I'm not a health professional but he sounds great, he sounds positive.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]